So Guy, Tessl have just released agent skill support.
What does that mean for people who have already built skills?
it means that you can treat those skills
as actual pieces of software, and not just words that you copy around.
You can package them up, version them, publish them for people to consume.
You can run some tests and evals to see if they're any good,
and you can own them over time and evolve them as the software
described, sort of evolves on its own.
The evals sound really interesting because I know there are tens
of thousands of skills out there, and I have no idea which ones to use.
how can evals help here?
So everything that we index in the registry, we immediately assess it.
We evaluate it and we give it a score.
So right away if you're looking for, you know, two things that help you
manipulate browsers.
Say you will see some score of, you know which one might be a little bit
better to use.
And you can drill down and get the details to understand,
you know, what does that mean and what's right for you.
That sounds super useful to work out which skills are most effective
in my environment.
Tell us a little bit more about the two different types of evals
that Tessl runs on your skills.
So one is called review eval and it's assessing whether a skill matches
the best practices.
That Anthropic put out for a skill.
Is it concise enough?
Is it split up into small files?
Does it have the right kind of activation instructions for the agent to load up?
That one we run on all the skills.
The second one is called task evaluation.
In that case we actually define a task that represents,
you know, what should this skill do?
And run an agent
through it with and without the skill and see how well it fares.
How much did the skill actually help?
Those are better, but they're a bit more tied to the evaluation data.
And they're just sort of heavier and more expensive to use.
So we have some of them and we will grow that list. Awesome.
And it really helps to know
which, skills really move the needle in more precise development with agents.
Amazing.
If you want to learn more, why don't you head over to tessl.io/registry,
where you can publish your own skills as well as learn and discover
about all the existing skills there today.